http://www.rbnz.govt.nz/privacy-and-disclaimer

Latest OCR
What is the Official Cash Rate?
Financial Stability Report
Macro-prudential policy (and LVRs)
Live-streams
C30 New residential mortgage lending by loan-to-valuation ratio (LVR)
Regulatory stocktake
Financial Sector Assessment Programme (FSAP)
Related websites
Collectable coins Section on NZ Post's website dedicated to buying collectable coins
B3 Retail interest rates on lending and deposits
B4 Foreign exchange turnover ($m daily averages)
B21 New residential mortgage special interest rates
B25 New interest bearing call savings account interest rates
B26 New interest bearing term deposit interest rates
B27 New interest bearing term PIE deposits interest rates
C5 Sector lending (banks and non-bank lending institutions)
C12 Credit card balances
C13 Credit card spending
C30 New residential mortgage lending by loan-to-valuation ratio (LVR)
C31 New residential mortgage lending by borrower type
C32 New and existing residential mortgage lending by payment type
C35 Residential mortgage loan reconciliation
C40 Residential mortgage lending by debt-to-income (DTI) purpose use
C41 Residential mortgage borrower gross income (BGI)
C50 Money and credit aggregates (depository corporations)
F5 Reserve Bank foreign currency assets and liabilities
R1 Reserve Bank balance sheet ($m)
R2 Reserve Bank statistical balance sheet ($m)
R3 Reserve Bank analytical accounts ($m)
NEW Bank Financial Strength Dashboard
S10 Banks: Balance sheet
S20 Banks: Summary income statement and related ratios
S21 Banks: Income statement ($m)
S30 Banks: Assets – Loans by sector
S31 Banks: Assets – Loans by purpose
S32 Banks: Assets – Loans by product
S33 Banks: Assets – Loans fully secured by residential mortgage by repricing
L2 Banks: Core funding ratio
L3 Banks: Face value of funding by residual maturity ($m)
J10 Insurance: Income Statement
J20 Insurance: Balance Sheet
T1 Non banks: Balance sheet ($m)
T4 Non banks: Funding and claims by sector ($m)
T11 Savings institutions: Balance sheet ($m)
T21 Deposit taking finance companies: Balance sheet ($m)
T31 Non-deposit taking finance companies: Balance sheet ($m)
T40 Funds under management ($m)
T41 Managed fund assets ($m)
T42 Life insurance ($m)
T43 KiwiSaver ($m)
T44 Other registered superannuation ($m)
T45 Retail unit trusts ($m)
T46 Cash management trusts ($m)
T47 Wholesale trusts ($m)
T48 Wholesale trusts and other funds ($m)
C21 Key household financial statistics ($m)
C22 Household balance sheet ($m)
M6 National accounts
M7 Balance of Payments and International Investment Position
E2 New Zealand's position with IMF
SDDS NZ's international reserves and foreign currency liquidity
Videos and speeches
Videos Media conferences, educational videos, presentations and lectures
Purpose
1. The purpose of this privacy policy is to let users of rbnz.govt.nz (the
"Site") know when we collect personal information and what we do
with it. We do not use, share or transfer personal information in connection
with the Site except as set out in this policy.
Collection, storage and use
2. There is no need to disclose personal information. The
Site can be viewed without the need to disclose any personal information to
us.
3. If you disclose personal information: You may choose to
disclose personal information when adding material to the Site. Such information
will be viewable by Site administrators, certain Reserve Bank of New Zealand
staff and contractors (including third parties who provide administration and/or
improvement services in relation to the Site) and, if published, members of the
public. Please do not post or otherwise transmit personal information of a
sensitive nature.
4. Storing information: Personal information that you
provide will be held by the Reserve Bank of New Zealand, and may be shared with,
and held by, Third Party Contractors to the extent necessary for those parties
to provide administration and/or improvement services in relation to the Site.
Email addresses provided when submitting forms or when emailing feedback
directly to the Reserve Bank are not made available to the public. Unless
required by law, we will not publicise the names or email addresses of
individuals who provide feedback to us without their consent.
5. Use of personal information: We use personal
information provided to us for the purpose of administering, evaluating and
improving the Site, improving our services and communicating with you. This information is retained and may be accessed or disclosed to third parties for analytics reporting and cyber security purposes.
6. Feedback: Feedback is important and is used to evaluate
and improve the Site. If you provide feedback on the Site directly to the
Reserve Bank of New Zealand via the supplied email address, that feedback will
be sent to appropriate RBNZ staff. We may pass on relevant comments to other
people within RBNZ who administer, have contributed content to, or are otherwise
interested in, the Site. This could include your email address and other
identifying information.
Statistical information and cookies
7. Statistical information collection: We collect
statistical information about your visit to help us improve the Site. This
information is aggregated and non-personally identifying.
8. Use of statistical information:
The statistical information referred to above will be viewable by Site administrators and certain other Reserve Bank staff.
9. Cookies: This site generates persistent session cookies
for the purpose of monitoring Site usage. The cookies do not collect personal
information. You can disable them or clear them out of the web browser you are
using to view this Site without affecting your ability to use the Site.
Records and disclosure statement
10. Public Records, Official Information and Parliament:
Your emails and contributions to the Site may constitute public records and be
retained to the extent required by the Public Records Act 2005. The Reserve Bank
may also be required by law to disclose those materials (for example, under the
Official Information Act 1982 or to a Parliamentary Select Committee).
Rights of access and correction
11. Your rights: Under the Privacy Act 1993, you have the
right to access and to request correction of any of your personal information
provided to the Reserve Bank of New Zealand in connection with your use of this
Site. If you would like to see the personal information relating to you that the
Reserve Bank has stored, or to change such personal information, or if you have
any concerns regarding your privacy, please contact us at the address set out
below. The Reserve Bank may require proof of your identity before being able to
provide you with any personal information.
12. Privacy Concerns: If you are not satisfied with our
response to any privacy-related concern you may have, you can contact the
Privacy Officer:
The Privacy Officer
Reserve Bank of New Zealand
PO Box
2498
Wellington
privacy@rbnz.govt.nz
Unsolicited email
Publication of email addresses on this site should not be taken as deemed consent to receiving unsolicited email. Persons or organisations wishing to send email material to individuals or organisations whose email addresses appear on this website must comply with the requirements of the Unsolicited Electronic Messages Act 2007.
Disclaimer
The Reserve Bank of New Zealand produces a variety of publications and
research dealing with monetary policy, financial stability, and related economic
and financial issues. Most are available without charge as part of the Reserve
Bank's public information service. For more information see our publications
section.
Every effort has been made by the Bank to ensure that material published on
this website is accurate and up to date. However, the Bank takes no
responsibility or accepts no liability arising from:
Errors or omissions
The way in which any material is interpreted
Reliance upon any material
The Bank is not responsible for the contents or reliability of
any linked websites and does not necessarily endorse the views expressed within
them.
Related to this page
Copyright
Accessibility
Social Media Policy
